University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1962-1972
  - 1965-1966
    - Public Work Department (Box 59:, Folder 914)
    - Recommendations (Box 59:, Folder 915)
    - Religious Education (Box 59:, Folder 916)
    - Research Foundation (Box 59:, Folder 917)
    - Research Grants (Box 59:, Folder 918-920)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 60:, Folder 921-923)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (Box 60:, Folder 924)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 60:, Folder 925)
    - State Health Department (Box 60:, Folder 926)
    - Stowe Prize Fund (Box 60:, Folder 927)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 60:, Folder 928-930)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 61:, Folder 931-933)
    - Taft School (Box 61:, Folder 934)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 61:, Folder 935)
    - Trees (Box 61:, Folder 936)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Dean, School of Social Work) (Box 61:, Folder 937)
    - U (Box 61:, Folder 938)
    - University Foundations (Box 61:, Folder 939-940)
    - University Secondary School [ E.O. Smith High School] (Box 61:, Folder 941)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 61:, Folder 942)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 61:, Folder 943)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 62:, Folder 944)
    - Westover School (Box 62:, Folder 945)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Dean, Graduate School) (Box 62:, Folder 946)
    - WHUS (Box 62:, Folder 947)
    - World Youth Forum, New York Herald-Tribune (Box 62:, Folder 948)
    - Yale Alumni Fund (Box 62:, Folder 949)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 62:, Folder 950)
    - Young, W. B. (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 62:, Folder 951)
  - 1966-1967
    - A (Box 62:, Folder 952)
    - AAA Mystery Tour (Box 62:, Folder 953)
    - Administrative Reports (Box 62:, Folder 954)
    - Advisors (Box 62:, Folder 955)
    - African Scholarship Program (Box 62:, Folder 956)
    - Agency of International Development (Box 62:, Folder 957)
    - Air Force (Box 62:, Folder 958)
    - Alumni (Box 62:, Folder 959)
    - American School for the Deaf -, Sunday, June 25 (Box 62:, Folder 960)
    - Arboretum (Box 62:, Folder 961)
    - Architects (Box 62:, Folder 962)
    - Attorney General (Box 62:, Folder 963)
    - B (Box 62:, Folder 964)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. - Personal mail (Box 62:, Folder 965)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. - Personal mail (Box 63:, Folder 966-968)
    - Bailey, Clark L. (Assistant to the President) (Box 63:, Folder 969)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 63:, Folder 970)
    - Bequests (Box 63:, Folder 971)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 63:, Folder 972)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 63:, Folder 973)
    - Brain Drain, The (Box 63:, Folder 974)
    - Braitmayer Foundation (Box 63:, Folder 975)
    - Brotman, Michael M. (Manager, Auditorium) (Box 63:, Folder 976)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 63:, Folder 977)
    - Budget, University (Box 63:, Folder 978)
    - C (Box 64:, Folder 979)
    - Capital Projects (Box 64:, Folder 980)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 64:, Folder 981)
    - Center for Italian Studies (Box 64:, Folder 982)
    - Center for Real State and Urban Economic Studies (Box 64:, Folder 983)
    - Christian, J.O. (Box 64:, Folder 984)
    - Civil Defense (Box 64:, Folder 985)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 64:, Folder 986)
    - Cohen, Sumner (Box 64:, Folder 987)
    - College Entrance Exam Board (Box 64:, Folder 988)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 64:, Folder 989)
    - Commencement (Box 64:, Folder 990)
    - Commission for Higher Education (Box 64:, Folder 991-992)
    - Committee on the Status of Women (Governor's) (Box 64:, Folder 993)
    - Committee
      - Athletic Advisory (Box 64:, Folder 994)
      - Advisory Center for Real Estate and Urban Economics (Box 64:, Folder 995)
      - Naming of Buildings (Box 64:, Folder 996)
      - Conditions of Student Life (Box 65:, Folder 997)
      - Library Advisory (Box 65:, Folder 998)
      - Traffic and Parking Policy ( E. J. R. Booth, Chmn) (Box 65:, Folder 999)
      - Advisory - Health Services (Box 65:, Folder 1000)
      - Advisory - Auditorium and Little Theater (Box 65:, Folder 1001)
      - Selection - 1967 Public Service Internships (Box 65:, Folder 1002)
      - Advisory - Radio and Television Center (Box 65:, Folder 1003)
      - Animal Care Facilities (Box 65:, Folder 1004)
      - Exhibits (Box 65:, Folder 1005)
      - Use of Humans in Research ( H. Clark) (Box 65:, Folder 1006)
      - Student-University Relations (Box 65:, Folder 1007)
      - University long-range planning (Box 65:, Folder 1008)
      - Curricula and Courses (Box 65:, Folder 1009)
      - Trustee, Administration, Faculty (Box 65:, Folder 1010)
    - Computer Center (Box 65:, Folder 1011)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 65:, Folder 1012)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 65:, Folder 1013)
    - Connecticut Education Association (Box 65:, Folder 1014)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 65:, Folder 1015)
    - Contracts (Box 65:, Folder 1016)
    - Council, Department - Anti-poverty Bill (Box 65:, Folder 1017)
    - Development, Plan of (through 1975) (Box 65:, Folder 1018)
    - Enrollments (Box 65:, Folder 1019)
    - F (Box 65:, Folder 1020)
    - Faculty-Alumni Center (Box 65:, Folder 1021-1023)
    - Faculty Children Exchange Program (Box 65:, Folder 1024)
    - Faculty Publications (Box 65:, Folder 1025)
    - Faculty Scholarships (Box 66:, Folder 1026)
    - Fairfield University (Box 66:, Folder 1027)
    - Finance and Control, State Department of (Box 66:, Folder 1028)
    - Farner, Frank (Box 66:, Folder 1029)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 66:, Folder 1030-1031)
    - Fingles, Franklin O., Registrar (Box 66:, Folder 1032)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 66:, Folder 1033)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 66:, Folder 1034)
    - Don Friedman, OPIP (Box 66:, Folder 1035)
    - Foreign Students (Box 66:, Folder 1036)
    - G (Box 66:, Folder 1037)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Box 66:, Folder 1038)
    - Glide - A - Ride (Box 66:, Folder 1039)
    - Governor of Connecticut (Box 66:, Folder 1040)
    - H (Box 66:, Folder 1041)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 66:, Folder 1042)
    - Hartford Hospital (Box 66:, Folder 1043)
    - Harvey, Robert O. (Dean, School of Business) (Box 66:, Folder 1044)
    - Health Center (Dr. Lewis Fox and Dr. John Patterson) (Box 67:, Folder 1045-1046)
    - Health Service (Dr. J. LeRoy) (Box 67:, Folder 1047)
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 67:, Folder 1048)
    - Hewit, Harold G. (Dean, School of Pharmacy) (Box 67:, Folder 1049)
    - Holt, Guy B., Trustee (Box 67:, Folder 1050)
    - Honors Program (Box 67:, Folder 1051)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. (Dean, School of Law) (Box 67:, Folder 1052)
    - I (Box 67:, Folder 1053)
    - Institute of
      - Cellular Biology (Box 67:, Folder 1054)
      - International Education (Box 67:, Folder 1055)
      - International and Intercultural Studies (Box 67:, Folder 1056)
      - Living (Box 67:, Folder 1057)
      - Marine Research (Box 67:, Folder 1058)
      - Materials Science (Box 67:, Folder 1059)
      - Public Service (Box 67:, Folder 1060)
      - Urban Research (Box 67:, Folder 1061)
      - Water Resources (Box 68:)
    - Jodaitis, Peter—Student Aid
    - Joint Projects Office
    - K
    - Kellogg Foundation
    - Kersting, Edward—Dean, College of Agriculture
    - L
    - Labor Education Center
    - Land-Grant College Association, (4 folders)
    - Legislation - Federal (Box 69:, Folder 1062)
    - Legislation - State (Box 69:, Folder 1063)
    - Library (Box 69:, Folder 1064)
    - Loeb File to WSM, 1965 November 26 (Box 69:, Folder 1065)
    - M (Box 69:, Folder 1066)
    - McCook Hospital (Box 69:, Folder 1067)
    - McCormick, Joseph (Trustee) (Box 69:, Folder 1068)
    - McMahon, Brien, Lecture series (Box 69:, Folder 1069)
    - Military Day, 1967 (Box 69:, Folder 1070)
    - Military Department (Box 69:, Folder 1071)
    - Mystic Seaport (Box 69:, Folder 1072)
    - N (Box 69:, Folder 1073)
    - National Board of Advisors - National Association for Retarded Children, 1967 April 27 (Box 69:, Folder 1074)
    - Naming of Buildings (Box 69:, Folder 1075)
    - National Scholarship Service and Fund or Negro Students (Box 69:, Folder 1076)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 69:, Folder 1077)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 69:, Folder 1078)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 70:, Folder 1079-1082)
    - New England Council (Box 70:, Folder 1083)
    - New England Presidents (Box 70:, Folder 1084)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 70:, Folder 1085)
    - Nolan, Francena (Dean) (Box 70:, Folder 1086)
    - Norris, Robert E. (Dean, Continuing Education Service) (Box 70:, Folder 1087)
    - O (Box 71:, Folder 1088)
    - Organization for Afro-American Students (Box 71:, Folder 1089)
    - Organization of Tropical Studies (Box 71:, Folder 1090)
    - P (Box 71:, Folder 1091)
    - Pomfret School (Box 71:, Folder 1092)
    - President's lecture series (Box 71:, Folder 1093)
    - President's Newsletter (Box 71:, Folder 1094)
    - Public Health Service - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities (Box 71:, Folder 1095)
    - Public Works Department (Box 71:, Folder 1096)
    - R (Box 71:, Folder 1097)
    - Radio and TV Center (Box 71:, Folder 1098)
    - Recreation program (Box 71:, Folder 1099)
    - Religious Education (Box 71:, Folder 1100)
    - Research Foundation (Box 71:, Folder 1101)
    - Research Grants (Box 71:, Folder 1102)
    - Rohrbach, John G. (Box 72:, Folder 1103)
    - S (Box 72:, Folder 1104)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 72:, Folder 1105-1109)
    - Security Insurance Group (Box 73:, Folder 1110)
    - Skating rink (Box 73:, Folder 1111)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 73:, Folder 1112)
    - State Health Department (Box 73:, Folder 1113)
    - State Highway Department (Box 73:, Folder 1114)
    - State Personnel Department (Box 73:, Folder 1115)
    - State Police Department (Box 73:, Folder 1116)
    - Student Senate (Box 73:, Folder 1117)
    - Student Union Board and Building (Box 73:, Folder 1118)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 73:, Folder 1119-1120)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 74:, Folder 1121)
    - T (Box 74:, Folder 1122)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 74:, Folder 1123)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Dean, School of Social Work) (Box 74:, Folder 1124)
    - U (Box 74:, Folder 1125)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 74:, Folder 1126-1127)
    - University Band (Box 74:, Folder 1128)
    - University Foundation (Box 74:, Folder 1129-1130)
    - University Scholars (Box 75:, Folder 1131)
    - University Security police (Box 75:, Folder 1132)
    - University Secondary School (Box 75:, Folder 1133)
    - University Senate (Box 75:, Folder 1134)
    - Upward Bound (Box 75:, Folder 1135)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 75:, Folder 1136)
    - Veterinary Medicine (Box 75:, Folder 1137)
    - Vlandis, John (Director of Admissions) (Box 75:, Folder 1138)
    - Van Bibber, E. George (Director, Physical Education) (Box 75:, Folder 1139)
    - W (Box 75:, Folder 1140)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 75:, Folder 1141)
    - Westover School (Box 75:, Folder 1142)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Dean, Graduate School) (Box 76:, Folder 1143)
    - Widmer, Carolyn (Dean, School of Nursing) (Box 76:, Folder 1144)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Dean, Arts and Sciences) (Box 76:, Folder 1145)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 76:, Folder 1146)
    - Young, W. B. (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 76:, Folder 1147)
  - 1967-1968
    - A (Box 76:, Folder 1148)
    - Administrative Reports (Box 76:, Folder 1149)
    - Advisers (Box 76:, Folder 1150)
    - Air Force (Box 76:, Folder 1151)
    - Alumni (Box 76:, Folder 1152)
    - American Council on Education (Box 76:, Folder 1153-1154)
    - April 26 Movement (Box 76:, Folder 1155)
    - Associated Student Government - Student Representation (Box 76:, Folder 1156)
    - Arons, Samuel D. Award (Box 76:, Folder 1157)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 76:, Folder 1158)
    - Attorney General (Box 76:, Folder 1159)
    - B (Box 76:, Folder 1160)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Trustee) (Box 76:, Folder 1161)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 76:, Folder 1162-1163)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 77:, Folder 1164-1168)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 78:, Folder 1169-1171)
    - Bailey, Clark L. (Box 78:, Folder 1172)
    - Bequests (Box 78:, Folder 1173)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 78:, Folder 1174)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 78:, Folder 1175)
    - Black Experience Forum, 1968 April 26 - 28 (Box 78:, Folder 1176)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 78:, Folder 1177)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 78:, Folder 1178)
    - Brain Drain (Box 78:, Folder 1179)
    - Brotman, Michael M. (Manager, Auditorium) (Box 78:, Folder 1180)
    - Buck, Raymond J. (Director, University Publications) (Box 78:, Folder 1181)
    - Budds, John J. (Box 78:, Folder 1182)
    - Budget, State (Box 78:, Folder 1183)
    - Budget, University (Box 78:, Folder 1184)
    - C (Box 78:, Folder 1185)
    - Capital Requests (Box 78:, Folder 1186)
    - Capital Projects (Box 79:, Folder 1187)
    - Center for Italian Studies (Box 79:, Folder 1188)
    - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies (Box 79:, Folder 1189)
    - Civil Defense (Box 79:, Folder 1190)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 79:, Folder 1191)
    - Cohen, Summer (Box 79:, Folder 1192)
    - Colfax Statement (Box 79:, Folder 1193)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 79:, Folder 1194)
    - Commencement, 1968 (Box 79:, Folder 1195)
    - Commission on Aid to Higher Education (Box 79:, Folder 1196)
    - Commission of Community Affairs ( LeRoy Jones, Commissioner) (Box 79:, Folder 1197)
    - Committees
      - Accident Prevention (Box 79:, Folder 1198)
      - Animal Care Facilities (Box 79:, Folder 1199)
      - Advisory - Athletics (Box 79:, Folder 1200)
      - Advisory - Auditorium and Little Theatre (Box 79:, Folder 1201)
      - Conditions of Student Life (Box 80:, Folder 1202)
      - Curricula and Courses (Box 80:, Folder 1203)
      - Data processing (Box 80:, Folder 1204)
      - Exhibits (Box 80:, Folder 1205)
      - Financial Assistance Policy (Box 80:, Folder 1206)
      - Advisory - Library (Box 80:, Folder 1207)
      - Minutes (Box 80:, Folder 1208)
      - Naming of Buildings (Box 80:, Folder 1209)
      - Placement Policy (Box 80:, Folder 1210)
      - Advisory - Publication Division (Box 80:, Folder 1211)
      - Reports (Box 80:, Folder 1212)
      - Status of Women (Box 80:, Folder 1213)
      - Student-University Relations (Box 80:, Folder 1214)
      - TAF (Box 80:, Folder 1215)
      - Traffic and Parking Review (Box 80:, Folder 1216)
      - Advisory - University Computer Center (Box 80:, Folder 1217)
      - Selection - Dental Dean (Box 80:, Folder 1218)
    - Compact of Education (Box 80:, Folder 1219)
    - Computer Center (Box 80:, Folder 1220)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 80:, Folder 1221)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education, (2 folders) (Box 80:, Folder 1222)
    - Connecticut Educational TV Corporation (Box 80:, Folder 1223)
    - Conn PEP - Connecticut Precollegiate Enrichment Program (Box 81:, Folder 1224)
    - Connecticut Geographic Information System (Box 81:, Folder 1225)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 81:, Folder 1226)
    - CONNTAC ( James E. Simmons, Director) (Box 81:, Folder 1227)
    - Consumer Day (Box 81:, Folder 1228)
    - Council for Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 81:, Folder 1229)
    - Council of State Governments - Committee on Legislative Modernization (Box 81:, Folder 1230)
    - D (Box 81:, Folder 1231)
    - Daily Campus (student newspaper) (Box 81:, Folder 1232)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 81:, Folder 1233)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Trustee) (Box 81:, Folder 1234)
    - Driscoll, Paul J. (Trustee) (Box 81:, Folder 1235)
    - E (Box 81:, Folder 1236)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 81:, Folder 1237)
    - Education, School of (Box 81:, Folder 1238)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 81:, Folder 1239)
    - Evans, John J. (Vice President, Financial Affairs) (Box 81:, Folder 1240)
    - F (Box 82:, Folder 1241)
    - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 82:, Folder 1242)
    - Faculty Publications (Box 82:, Folder 1243)
    - Faculty Salaries (Box 82:, Folder 1244)
    - Faculty Scholarships (Box 82:, Folder 1245)
    - Faculty Salaries (Box 82:, Folder 1246)
    - Faculty Scholarships (Box 82:, Folder 1247)
    - Fees (Box 82:, Folder 1248)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Registrar) (Box 82:, Folder 1249)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 82:, Folder 1250-1251)
    - Finance and Control, State Department of (Box 82:, Folder 1252)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 82:, Folder 1253)
    - Foreign Students (Box 82:, Folder 1254)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 82:, Folder 1255)
    - Friedman, Don (Office of Public Information) (Box 82:, Folder 1256)
    - Fuller, Alfred C., (Trustee) (Box 82:, Folder 1257)
    - G (Box 82:, Folder 1258)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Academic Vice President) (Box 82:, Folder 1259)
    - Gill, Eleanor (Dean, School of Nursing) (Box 83:, Folder 1260)
    - Gill, Joseph (Trustee) (Box 83:, Folder 1261)
    - Governor of Connecticut (Box 83:, Folder 1262)
    - Governor's Conference on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 83:, Folder 1263)
    - H (Box 83:, Folder 1264)
    - Halpert Exhibition (Box 83:, Folder 1265)
    - Hampton Institute (Box 83:, Folder 1266)
    - Hansen, Henry (Box 83:, Folder 1267)
    - Hartford - Babbidge meeting 1/25 (Box 83:, Folder 1268)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 83:, Folder 1269)
    - Hartford Hospital (Box 83:, Folder 1270)
    - Harvey, Robert O. (Dean, School of Business Administration) (Box 83:, Folder 1271)
    - Haskins Laboratories (Box 83:, Folder 1272)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 83:, Folder 1273)
    - Health Service (Box 84:, Folder 1274-1276)
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 84:, Folder 1277)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. (Dean, School of Pharmacy) (Box 84:, Folder 1278)
    - Hickey, James E. (Directory of Athletics) (Box 84:, Folder 1279)
    - Holt, Guy B. (Trustee) (Box 84:, Folder 1280)
    - Honors Program (Box 84:, Folder 1281)
    - I (Box 84:, Folder 1282)
    - Inner City Program (Box 84:, Folder 1283)
    - Institute of
      - International Education (Box 84:, Folder 1284)
      - International and Intercultural Studies (Box 84:, Folder 1285)
      - Living (Box 84:, Folder 1286)
      - Marine Research (Box 84:, Folder 1287)
      - Material Science (Box 84:, Folder 1288)
      - Public Service (Box 84:, Folder 1289)
      - Urban Research (Box 85:, Folder 1290)
      - Water Resources (Box 85:, Folder 1291)
    - International Silver prize medal (annual) (Box 85:, Folder 1292)
    - J (Box 85:, Folder 1293)
    - Jodaitis, Peter (Box 85:, Folder 1294)
    - Joint projects office (Box 85:, Folder 1295)
    - K (Box 85:, Folder 1296)
    - Kammer, Harry (Box 85:, Folder 1297)
    - Kersting, Edwin (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 85:, Folder 1298)
    - King, Martin Luther, Foundation (Box 85:, Folder 1299)
    - Land-Grant College Association (Box 85:, Folder 1300-1301)
    - Langrock, David Theodore (Box 86:, Folder 1302)
    - Legislation, Federal (Box 86:, Folder 1303)
    - Legislation, State (Box 86:, Folder 1304)
    - Legislation Forum (Box 86:, Folder 1305)
    - Library (Box 86:, Folder 1306)
    - Loeb Awards (Box 86:, Folder 1307)
    - Long-range Planning Committee (Box 86:, Folder 1308)
    - Lumsden Report (Box 86:, Folder 1309)
    - M (Box 86:, Folder 1310)
    - Manning, Stuart (Summer Session, Credit Extension) (Box 86:, Folder 1311)
    - Maxcy, Ellis C. (Box 86:, Folder 1312)
    - McCormick, Joseph (Trustee) (Box 86:, Folder 1313)
    - McMahon, Brien, Lecture Series (Box 86:, Folder 1314)
    - Military Department (Box 86:, Folder 1315)
    - Moreland, Wallace (Box 86:, Folder 1316)
    - Museum of Art (Box 86:, Folder 1317)
    - Mystic Seaport (Box 86:, Folder 1318)
    - N (Box 86:, Folder 1319)
    - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities (Box 86:, Folder 1320)
    - National Education Association (Box 87:, Folder 1321)
    - National School Service and Fund for Negro Students (Box 87:, Folder 1322)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 87:, Folder 1323)
    - Newcomen Society (Box 87:, Folder 1324)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 87:, Folder 1325)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 87:, Folder 1326)
    - New England Presidents (Box 87:, Folder 1327)
    - New England Presidents - Faculty children Exchange Program (Box 87:, Folder 1328)
    - New England Council (Box 87:, Folder 1329)
    - New England Research Applications Center (Box 87:, Folder 1330)
    - Nielsen, Carl W. (Trustee) (Box 87:, Folder 1331)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 88:, Folder 1332)
    - Norris, Robert B. (Dean, Continuing Education) (Box 88:, Folder 1333)
    - O (Box 88:, Folder 1334)
    - Oral History Project (Box 88:, Folder 1335)
    - Organization for Afro-American Students (Box 88:, Folder 1336)
    - Organization of Tropical Studies (Box 88:, Folder 1337)
    - P (Box 88:, Folder 1338)
    - Peace Corps (Box 88:, Folder 1339)
    - Plans for Development (Box 88:, Folder 1340)
    - Powers, John (Placement) (Box 88:, Folder 1341)
    - President's Lecture Series (Box 88:, Folder 1342)
    - President's Newsletter (Box 88:, Folder 1343)
    - Project Nehemiah - Center for Choice (Box 88:, Folder 1344)
    - Public Service Internships (Box 88:, Folder 1345)
    - Public Works Department (Box 88:, Folder 1346)
    - R (Box 88:, Folder 1347)
    - Radio - TV Center (Box 88:, Folder 1348)
    - Re (Box 89:, Folder 1349)
    - Recommendations (Box 89:, Folder 1350)
    - Recruitment Policy (Box 89:, Folder 1351)
    - Religious Education (Box 89:, Folder 1352)
    - Research Foundation (Box 89:, Folder 1353)
    - Research Grants (Box 89:, Folder 1354-1356)
    - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 90:, Folder 1357)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 90:, Folder 1358)
    - Rohrbach, John G. (Box 90:, Folder 1359)
    - S (Box 90:, Folder 1360)
    - Sacks, Howard R. (Dean, School of Law) (Box 90:, Folder 1361)
    - Sadik, Marvin ( University Museum of Art) (Box 90:, Folder 1362)
    - Saint Francis Hospital (Box 90:, Folder 1363)
    - Sanders, William J. (Trustee) (Box 90:, Folder 1364)
    - Sch (Box 90:, Folder 1365)
    - Se (Box 90:, Folder 1366)
    - Semester on the 1930s (Box 90:, Folder 1367)
    - Sh (Box 90:, Folder 1368)
    - Si (Box 90:, Folder 1369)
    - Skating Rink (Box 90:, Folder 1370)
    - Ski Slope (Box 90:, Folder 1371)
    - Southeastern Branch - Avery Point (Box 90:, Folder 1372)
    - St (Box 90:, Folder 1373)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 90:, Folder 1374)
    - State Building Commission (Box 90:, Folder 1375)
    - State Comptroller (Box 90:, Folder 1376)
    - State Development (Box 90:, Folder 1377)
    - State Department of Health (Box 90:, Folder 1378)
    - State Highway Department (Box 90:, Folder 1379)
    - State Personnel Department (Box 90:, Folder 1380)
    - State Police Department (Box 90:, Folder 1381)
    - State Prison (Box 90:, Folder 1382)
    - State Welfare Department (Box 90:, Folder 1383)
    - Sterling, M. Elizabeth (Trustee) (Box 90:, Folder 1384)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 90:, Folder 1385)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 91:, Folder 1386)
    - Student Insurance (Box 91:, Folder 1387)
    - Student Life (Box 91:, Folder 1388)
    - Student Senate (Box 91:, Folder 1389)
    - Student Union (Box 91:, Folder 1390)
    - Symposium for Trustees (Box 91:, Folder 1391-1392)
    - T (Box 91:, Folder 1393)
    - Taft School (Box 91:, Folder 1394)
    - Tickers (Box 91:, Folder 1395)